Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
So after these obsessions are eliminated,
وبعد التخلص من هذه الهواجس،
will she really vanish into thin air?
هل ستختفي حقا في الهواء؟
Sins.
الخطايا.
will always be repaid one day.
سيتم سدادها دائمًا يومًا ما.
When that day comes,
عندما يأتي ذلك اليوم،
all traces of her existence in this world
كل آثار وجودها في هذا العالم
will be erased.
سيتم مسحها.
Vanished without a trace.
اختفى دون أن يترك أثرا.
Spirit Lady,
سيدة الروح،
if you have a way for me to help her escape the karmic fire,
إذا كان لديك طريقة لمساعدتها على الهروب من النار الكرمية،
you must also have a way
يجب أن يكون لديك طريقة أيضًا
for me to help her change her fate.
لكي أساعدها في تغيير مصيرها.
The one who tied the knot
الذي عقد قرانه
must be the one to untie it.
يجب أن يكون الشخص الذي يفكه.
Only when she truly lets go of her obsessions
فقط عندما تتخلى حقًا عن هواجسها
will it be possible
هل سيكون ذلك ممكنا
to rewrite her fate.
لإعادة كتابة مصيرها.
You and she share a thousand-year bond.
أنت وهي تربطكما رابطة تمتد لألف عام.
Now,
الآن،
if you join forces with her,
إذا انضممت إليها،
there might be a glimmer of hope.
ربما يكون هناك بصيص أمل.
Hey, Qin.
مهلا، تشين.
Dongfang.
دونغفانغ.
Come save me quickly!
تعال وأنقذني بسرعة!
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Please come rescue me now!
من فضلك تعال وأنقذني الآن!
Someone wants to kill me.
أحدهم يريد قتلي.
Where are you now?
أين أنت الآن؟
Who wants to kill you?
من يريد قتلك؟
It's one of my clients.
إنه أحد عملائي.
Her mother suspects I'm seducing her daughter.
والدتها تشك بأنني أغوي ابنتها.
I'll go there now.
سأذهب إلى هناك الآن.
Mr. Dongfang.
السيد دونغفانغ.
Oh no!
أوه لا!
Mr. Dongfang isn't planning to escape, is he?
السيد دونغفانغ لا يخطط للهروب، أليس كذلك؟
I need to tell the manager about this right away.
أريد أن أخبر المدير بهذا الأمر على الفور.
You can't go.
لا يمكنك الذهاب.
If the manager finds out I let it slip,
إذا اكتشف المدير أنني تركت الأمر يفلت مني،
he'll skin me alive.
سوف يسلخني حيًا.
What should we do then?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل إذن؟
What is it that I shouldn't know about?
ما هو الشيء الذي لا ينبغي لي أن أعرفه؟
Calm down.
اهدأ.
You bastard!
أيها الوغد!
Bastard!
نذل!
What took you so long?
ما الذي أخذ منك كل هذا الوقت؟
Ma'am,
سيدتي،
let's talk this through, okay?
دعونا نتحدث عن هذا الأمر، حسنًا؟
you've really misunderstood.
لقد أساءت الفهم حقًا.
Misunderstood?
هل أسيء فهمك؟
Haitang and I
هايتانج وأنا
are simply in a therapist-patient relationship,
هم ببساطة في علاقة معالج-مريض،
nothing more.
لا شيء أكثر.
You've clearly been planning this all along.
من الواضح أنك كنت تخطط لهذا طوال الوقت.
You just want to get close to my daughter.
تريد فقط أن تقترب من ابنتي.
Ma'am...
سيدتي...
How dare you make excuses!
كيف تجرؤ على تقديم الأعذار!
Oh no,
أوه لا،
ma'am.
سيدتي.
Please calm down.
من فضلك اهدأ.
There must be a misunderstanding.
لابد أن يكون هناك سوء فهم.
Misunderstanding?
سوء الفهم؟
Who do you think you are?
من تعتقد نفسك؟
What's it got to do with you?
ما علاقة هذا بك؟
My daughter graduated from a prestigious university.
لقد تخرجت ابنتي من جامعة مرموقة.
She's perfectly healthy.
إنها بصحة جيدة تماما.
What psychological problems could she possibly have?
ما هي المشاكل النفسية التي من الممكن أن تعاني منها؟
It's clearly that beast in human clothing
من الواضح أن هذا الوحش في ملابس بشرية
using therapy as a front
استخدام العلاج كواجهة
just to take advantage of my daughter.
فقط للاستفادة من ابنتي.
Running away, are you?
هل أنت تهرب؟
I'll smash this whole place up!
سأحطم هذا المكان بأكمله!
Hey!
يا!
No, don't!
لا لا تفعل ذلك!
You'll hurt your hand.
سوف تؤذي يدك.
Dr. Qin knew nothing about this.
ولم يكن الدكتور تشين يعرف شيئًا عن هذا.
Please stop blaming him, okay?
من فضلك توقف عن إلقاء اللوم عليه، حسنًا؟
Zou Haitang,
زو هايتانج,
shut your mouth!
اصمت!
I'll deal with you when we get home.
سأتعامل معك عندما نصل إلى المنزل.
Ma'am, let's sit down and talk.
سيدتي، دعونا نجلس ونتحدث.
Take your hands off me.
ارفع يديك عني.
I see
أرى
you and that beast
أنت وهذا الوحش
are birds of a feather.
هم طيور من نفس النوع.
Hey!
يا!
Stay away from my daughter and me.
ابتعد عني وعن ابنتي.
Boss.
رئيس.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
If I hadn't come,
لو لم آتي،
you would've been beaten to death.
لقد تم ضربك حتى الموت.
Be careful.
احرص.
I'm already an adult.
أنا شخص بالغ بالفعل.
Why won't you give me
لماذا لا تعطيني
even a little bit of freedom?
حتى القليل من الحرية؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Haitang.
هايتانج.
Haitang, what's wrong?
هايتانج، ما الخطب؟
What's wrong, Haitang?
ما الأمر يا هايتانج؟
Haitang.
هايتانج.
Don't scare mommy.
لا تخيف أمي.
Mom is only doing what's best for you.
أمك تفعل فقط ما هو الأفضل لك.
Haitang.
هايتانج.
We should be able to see her again soon.
ينبغي أن نكون قادرين على رؤيتها مرة أخرى قريبا.
I need to tell Qin Qi.
أريد أن أخبر تشين تشي.
He doesn't know about this girl's situation.
إنه لا يعرف شيئًا عن حالة هذه الفتاة.
This person
هذا الشخص
Don't see him again in the future.
لن أراه مرة أخرى في المستقبل.
He's not as simple as you think.
إنه ليس بسيطا كما تعتقد.
Why?
لماذا؟
He's my good friend.
إنه صديقي الجيد.
Suit yourself.
تناسب نفسك.
So strange.
غريب جداً.
The way that girl was acting just now.
الطريقة التي كانت تتصرف بها تلك الفتاة للتو.
Her mother still had to come find you.
لا يزال يتعين على والدتها أن تأتي للبحث عنك.
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
She's just crazy.
إنها مجنونة فقط.
What's really going on with this girl?
ماذا يحدث حقا مع هذه الفتاة؟
Why is she so frightening when she eats?
لماذا هي مخيفة جداً عندما تأكل؟
She has serious emotional issues.
إنها تعاني من مشاكل عاطفية خطيرة.
If this continues,
إذا استمر هذا،
not only will her emotions collapse,
لن تنهار عواطفها فحسب،
but her body won't hold up either.
ولكن جسدها لن يصمد أيضًا.
It's all because of her mother,
كل هذا بسبب والدتها
caused by excessive control over a long period.
ناجمة عن السيطرة المفرطة لفترة طويلة.
She is quite pitiful indeed.
إنها مثيرة للشفقة حقا.
When her heart can't bear it anymore,
عندما لم يعد قلبها يتحمل ذلك،
she finds comfort in food.
إنها تجد الراحة في الطعام.
Alright,
على ما يرام،
let's not talk about her anymore.
دعونا لا نتحدث عنها بعد الآن.
How have you been lately?
كيف حالك في الآونة الأخيرة؟
I'm doing great at the inn.
أنا بخير في النزل.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك
our inn is really interesting.
نزلنا مثير للاهتمام حقًا.
There's this total bootlicker,
هناك هذا المتملق الكامل،
and there's also a little pig spirit.
وهناك أيضًا روح الخنزير الصغيرة.
A pig spirit!
روح الخنزير!
Your condition is getting worse.
حالتك تتدهور.
You should come to me for treatment for a while.
ينبغي عليك أن تأتي إلي لتلقي العلاج لفترة من الوقت.
You don't understand.
أنت لا تفهم.
Innkeeper,
صاحب النزل،
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
Mr. Dongfang,
السيد دونغفانغ،
the innkeeper doesn't seem to be in a good mood.
يبدو أن صاحب النزل ليس في مزاج جيد.
Newcomer,
الوافد الجديد،
weren't you leaving?
ألم تكن مسافرا؟
Why are you back again?
لماذا عدت مرة أخرى؟
Innkeeper.
صاحب النزل.
The rice is cold.
الرز بارد.
I made some noodles for you.
لقد صنعت لك بعض المعكرونة.
I'll go.
سأذهب.
Zou Haitang.
زو هايتانج.
Why is she here?
لماذا هي هنا؟
Isn't it because you brought her from the healing room?
أليس هذا لأنك أحضرتها من غرفة الشفاء؟
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
that she's our next client?
أنها عميلتنا القادمة؟
What should we do with her now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل معها الآن؟
Throw her out.
اطردها.
She'll forget everything that happened today by tomorrow anyway.
إنها سوف تنسى كل ما حدث اليوم بحلول الغد على أية حال.
That won't do,
هذا لن يفعل
boss.
رئيس.
Is this how you've been treating your clients?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تعامل بها عملائك؟
No wonder the complaint rate is so high.
فلا عجب أن معدل الشكاوى مرتفع جدًا.
I don't need you telling me how to do my job.
لا أحتاج منك أن تخبرني كيف أقوم بعملي.
Since she's a client,
بما أنها عميلة،
we should treat her properly.
ينبغي علينا أن نعاملها بشكل صحيح.
Besides, the deeper her obsession,
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، كلما كان هوسها أعمق،
the more it will benefit you once it's resolved.
كلما كان ذلك مفيدًا لك بمجرد حله.
Take him to a guest room.
أخذه إلى غرفة الضيوف.
Clean it up quickly.
نظفه بسرعة.
Don't delay our inn's business.
لا تؤخر أعمال نزلنا.
Yes, innkeeper!
نعم يا صاحب النزل!
My knife!
سكيني!
Who came last night?
من جاء الليلة الماضية؟
The edge of my knife is all bent.
حافة سكينتي كلها منحنية.
Stop arguing.
توقف عن الجدال.
It was the new guest who arrived yesterday.
لقد كان الضيف الجديد الذي وصل بالأمس.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I've caused trouble for everyone.
لقد تسببت في مشاكل للجميع.
Coming to someone's place without notice,
القدوم إلى مكان شخص ما دون سابق إنذار،
messing with other people's things,
العبث بأشياء الآخرين،
you should be thrown out!
ينبغي أن يتم طردك!
Calm down.
اهدأ.
I truly apologize.
أنا أعتذر حقا.
I'll definitely clean up the inn.
سأقوم بتنظيف النزل بالتأكيد.
And I'll compensate everyone for the damaged items.
وسوف أقوم بتعويض الجميع عن العناصر التالفة.
Can you even afford it?
هل تستطيع تحمل تكاليف ذلك؟
Come on.
تعال.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
It's okay, don't blame yourself.
لا بأس، لا تلوم نفسك.
You didn't do it on purpose.
لم تفعل ذلك عمدا.
We'll restore everything to its original state.
سوف نقوم باستعادة كل شيء إلى حالته الأصلية.
But,
لكن،
what happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
Since you've come to the Monster Inn,
بما أنك أتيت إلى Monster Inn،
you are our guest.
أنت ضيفنا.
Why don't we...
لماذا لا نفعل...
go upstairs and have a proper talk?
اصعد إلى الطابق العلوي وأجري محادثة مناسبة؟
You two,
انتما الاثنان
continue cleaning.
استمرار التنظيف.
Yes, innkeeper!
نعم يا صاحب النزل!
Do you know where this place is?
هل تعرف أين هذا المكان؟
No, I don't.
لا أنا لا.
Then how did you get here?
ثم كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
I followed you all the way here.
لقد اتبعتك طوال الطريق إلى هنا.
But as soon as I arrived,
ولكن بمجرد وصولي،
I started feeling very hungry again,
بدأت أشعر بالجوع الشديد مرة أخرى،
and then I lost consciousness.
وبعدها فقدت الوعي.
May I ask where this is?
هل يمكنني أن أسأل أين هذا؟
This is the Monster Inn.
هذا هو نزل الوحش.
This place
هذا المكان
isn't somewhere just anyone can come to.
ليس مكانًا يمكن لأي شخص أن يأتي إليه.
Monster Inn?
نزل الوحش؟
So are you all
هل أنتم جميعا كذلك؟
monsters?
الوحوش؟
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
We won't hurt you.
لن نؤذيك
Do you need our help?
هل تحتاج مساعدتنا؟
Tell us.
أخبرنا.
Perhaps
ربما
we can help you.
يمكننا مساعدتك.
Are you going to talk?
هل ستتحدث؟
If not, then leave.
وإن لم يكن كذلك، فارحل.
Go home.
اذهب إلى المنزل.
No, no, no.
لا، لا، لا.
I won't go home.
لن أعود إلى المنزل.
I don't want to see her.
لا أريد رؤيتها.
Who is she?
من هي؟
She's my mom.
إنها أمي.
My mom is very good to me.
أمي طيبة جدًا معي.
She loves me so much.
إنها تحبني كثيرا.
She loves me to the point
إنها تحبني إلى حد ما
that it suffocates me.
إنه يخنقني.
Haitang.
هايتانج.